Today is sixty-four again.
Helping Caio wash the shed.
That's too much of a clown,
man.
Worth my partner.
Okay,
our lady Juninho,
today we're screwed.
Here is bro.
I'm going to do the event in an abandoned shed,
right?
Who wants what my partner takes out of the dirt.
I'll put a little son for us.
Juninho,
galley from the gas station here,
mobilized to help clean up.
Bro,
now we're in the fantastic quartet,
reached the chairs bro
I ordered 60 chairs if there are more people,
I can manage to borrow some chairs down there at the gas station.
It's on now I need to assemble
The boss.
I was sick now.
You can't use a car because you didn't work or live.
Look at this deal here,
uncle.
Look how many chairs?
Almost everything is ready for what I'm preparing to do.
At that first moment of this idea,
I thought I'd invite local merchants here in town.
I confess to you that you are one.
An adrenaline.
Are you on, bro?
It's a mixture of feelings like that,
man,
look at the time I'm doing it,
I've been on and rooting for the guys to stick it out too,
now all that comes to my mind is trying to make the
best material possible for the people who have here,
being able to absorb a great content.
The message has to be bigger than the messenger.
I hope it works.
I'll stay with you until tomorrow.
Like to help your Son,
but you're too young to vote.